When did you figure it out?
- How did you know?
- Shut up.
But how did you find out?
Shut it.
- Are you staying late?
- I'll be heading home soon.
Lunch was so good today.
Sir!
Ah, Hyun Jae!
Good afternoon, sir.
Did you have lunch yet?
I did, sir.
Long time no see, Hyun Jae.
- Producer Lee, sir.
- How have you been?
Fine, sir.
Good afternoon.
Is this the first time you two are seeing
each other since the survival program?
Oh, well... I guess it is.
Hyun Jae. I heard you have an album
coming out by the end of the year.
That's right, sir.
So you're a proper artist now, aren't you?
Hey, Hyun Jae.
Be grateful to the CEO, you hear me?
Hey, come on, now.
He's doing wonderfully already.
Hyun Jae!
Good afternoon, sir.
What? You're here as well?
I am, sir.
Unicorn.
Oh, I remember.
Right, you had a merger with Unicorn.
Fate works in mysterious ways, isn't that so?
You're pretty unfortunate.
- Let's head inside, Producer Lee.
- All right.
- I'm starving. Let's go.
- Okay.
What's going on?
What's with them?
Jae Min!
Now, look here.
"Shin Jae Min, wrongly accused of stalking,
is not who we all thought he was."
I know you've been having a hard time.
We've got your back now.
So do your best, too, Jae Min.
Okay?
Hey, look at that.
The internet loves you, too.
"Justice for Jae Min..."
[You can see it in his face,
Jae Min didn't do anything wrong!]
The press took pretty well to it, too.
Give it a good, clean ending, you hear?
You know, like those stories about karma.
It's a great song, don't you think?
Well? It's good, right?
- Yes, sir.
- See? I told you, didn't I?
There's nothing this guy can't do.
He's a genius. A genius!
Thank you, sir.
Stop being so modest.
I knew you had it in you from the start.
All right, everyone. We'll start
practicing with this demo track for now.
Anyone have any thoughts on this?
All right.
It's a good song, no doubt.
Great, then, let's get it on, boys!
Khun, you stay for a second.
Well, you see...
about the lyrics...
Just translating everything in Korean isn't it.
If it's all just Korean, Korean,
it's going to sound bland. Not to good taste.
So get a good translator, give it some flavor.
It needs that zing, you see...
- That was incredible.
- Just our style.
I prefer my songs harder.
It suits you perfectly, though.
It's like it was written specifically for you.
Really?
I don't know about that.
Oh, stop playing dumb.
It hits you the second you hear it, right?
That's your song.
Is that so?
Aw, look at Jae Min, all set up for success.
Stop it, that's not true.
What is it?
Hey, Jae min.
I'm sorry... for misjudging you.
I'm sorry, too.
Let bygones be bygones.
Hey, Khun.
I'm sorry... about that time.
If you're really sorry, bottoms up.
Come on, there's no way.
You Thai guys are a different breed!
- Show us! Drink!
- Chug it, chug it!
Bottoms up! Cheers!
- Cheers!
Jae Min.
That was good.
Thank you, sir.
Good job, everybody!
You worked hard!
Your team's having another get-together?
I'm jealous of you guys.
Where are you?
Okay, don't overdo it.
Get home safe.
Do you...
want to grab dinner with me?
Khun must be at the get-together, so...
I just got invited to hang out.
I'm hanging up.
[Wanna sneak out?]
[Yoon Soo An, I said let's go!]
I need to use the restroom.
Huh? What are you doing here?
I kept texting you.
Why did you ignore them?
You texted me?
I didn't get any...
[Block this number]
Did you block my number?
Wait, no, it's not like that.
Give it back.
- Give it back, now!
- Just wait.
Wait, let me see.
What is this?
What do you mean?
This text.
[I miss you, Hyun Jae. Don't you miss me?]
Did you send this to me?
You left me on read, remember?
Or do you, what,
feel sorry for me?
It's fine now.
No, it's not that.
I never got this text.
I've never seen it before.
That makes no sense.
What is it?
Is something wrong?
This is the day...
they took my phone away.
I'm sorry.
For not clearing it up sooner.
Don't apologize. It's not your fault.
Okay?
It's all water under the bridge now.
Let's just move forward.
I like how things are right now.
Then...
That text...
Can I give you my answer now?
[CEO Goo Sang Cheol]
Kim Hyun Jae.
Want to hear something funny?
Failed yet again.
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
What's this?
[Il Woo, why aren't you answering?]
Il Woo disclosed the texts and calls,
and they're taking legal action.
These texts were fabricated
and bent to fit their agenda.
We should put out our own side of the story
and take legal action...
Manager Park.
Why do you think I picked Jae Min?